in today's world not all superheroes
wear capes meet vikas an ordinary man
with extraordinary responsibilities to
fulfill these responsibilities he has a
superpower introducing ICICI prove
protect and gain a plan that empowers
him to secure his family's financial
future and his dreams it provides
comprehensive protection to his family
including life
cover accidental death
cover and accidental disability
cover vikas will get a lumpsum on policy
maturity to fulfill his goals and with
easy documentation it is quite simple to
buy so let us see how this plan works
for example at 35 vikas pays an annual
premium of 62 , 63 rupees for 10 years
for a policy term of 40
years in case of his death during the
policy term his family will get a live
cover of 50 lakh rupees and the policy
will terminate in the event of an
accidental death the nominee will
receive an additional cover of 50 lakh
rupees resulting in a total benefit of 1
CR rupees consequently the policy will
terminate in casee of permanent
disability due to an accident he will
get a lumpsum of 50 lakh rupees and the
policy benefits
continue on Survival vigas will get
Market linked returns as a lumsum at the
age of 75 to fulfill his dreams this
plan helps vas to protect his family
financially in his absence and also
helps him secure hisam dreams for a long
and fulfilling
life be a pro like a superhero with
ICICI Pro protect and
[Music]
Gain